http://www.imaging-in-italy.com/privacy

Home/
OUR TOURS/Rome ToursFlorence Half-Day TourFlorence, Chianti & Tuscany ToursVenice ToursMurano-BuranoPortrait ToursPhoto Gallery
Privacy/
Imaging In Italy - Private photo tours of Rome, Florence, Tuscany and Venice
Privacy Policy
Imaging In Italy - photo tours in Rome, Florence & Venice: We take your privacy seriously.  Read about our privacy policies here.
Home/
OUR TOURS/Rome ToursFlorence Half-Day TourFlorence, Chianti & Tuscany ToursVenice ToursMurano-BuranoPortrait ToursPhoto Gallery
PRIVACY POLICY
We take your privacy seriously. Please review our privacy policy before you send us any information.The purpose of this policy is to document the rights and confidentiality afforded to all the visitors to the Imaging In Italy web site (www.Imaging-in-Italy.com & www.imaginginitaly.com). Imaging In Italy follows the procedures set forth below to safeguard your privacy on-line. Please read the following policy to understand how we handle your personal information. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.When do we ask for personal information?An anonymous visitor to our site remains anonymous. We do not attempt to identify visitors if they do not voluntarily register on our site.How personal information is collected and distributedWe collect personal information from you in only one place on our webpage.   We intend to inform you in advance and grant you the option not to continue. The Imaging In Italy web site collects no personally identifiable information unless provided explicitly by the user. If you choose not to provide the requested information, you still can access most of the Imaging In Italy website; however, you may be unable to register for our tours.Imaging In Italy manages and catalogs all its information gathered off the website with care. All information collected at this site is kept strictly confidential and is not intended to be shared, commercially sold, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed to persons other than Imaging In Italy's representatives and distributors.Typical Examples of when and why we ask for Personal Information:To process a reservation requestTo email invoicesTo send out update notices and announcementsTo help improve our offeringsTo address customer support related issuesTo register for our workshops, tours, etc.To request a shipping address if necessary to complete registration.Privacy of our email listsFor particular product inquiries, we may ask that you supply us with an email address in order to register for our tours and/or respond to your inquiry.  In order to respond to your inquiries, we require only that you provide us with a valid email address, your full name, the city, state, zip code, and country of your residence. Additional information such as telephone, fax, and mobile phone numbers and other incidental information may be provided if you wish, but is not mandatory.  Imaging In Italy does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any of the email addresses  or other information on our list to anyone outside of  Imaging In Italy's marketing partners, or authorized Imaging In Italy distributors.How Imaging In Italy is securing your privacyAny information that you choose to provide us with is handled in a respectful manner. Our primary goal is to better understand your needs and provide you with superior customer service.Responses to legal processNotwithstanding the foregoing, if Imaging In Italy receives due legal process, Imaging In Italy may disclose information provided to us through our web site.QuestionsImaging In Italy welcomes comments and questions on this policy. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information. Due to the rapidly evolving technologies on the Internet, we may occasionally update this policy. All revisions will be posted to this site. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at info@imaging-in-italy.com
Home/
OUR TOURS/Rome ToursFlorence Half-Day TourFlorence, Chianti & Tuscany ToursVenice ToursMurano-BuranoPortrait ToursPhoto Gallery
Packages/
Pricing & Reservations/
Contact Us/
Your Guides/
Testimonials/
FAQ/FAQTOUR AGREEMENT
Privacy/
Imaging In Italy - Photo Tours in Rome, Florence & Venice
Personal private photo walking tour of Rome, Florence, and Venice. Take an engaging walking photo tour and an unforgettable photographic adventure. Let us show you how to bring history alive through photography.   We offer a variety of photo tours to suit your needs and schedule.
Quick Contact
Your Email Address
*
We will not share this with anyone not connected to Imaging in Italy
Your Name
*
Please give us your full name.
Thank you.
First Name
Last Name
Comments
& Inquiries
Thank you!
IMAGING IN ITALY1102 West Glass AvenueSpokane, Washington, 99205 USATel: +1 509 435 2921 info@imaging-in-italy.com
Copyright © 2004-2019 Imaging in Italy | Private Photo Tours in Rome, Florence, Tuscany & VenicePowered by Squarespace
